<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[IT Support | Vancouver]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[IT Support | Vancouver]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/israel-acosta/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2016 17:16:56 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/israel-acosta/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[resume]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p> Israel Acosta E-Mail: israel-acosta@hotmail.com 778-994-4996 LinkedIn: http://goo.gl/zIS2Z israelacosta.com Vancouver, BC. Objective Seeking an opportunity in Network Security and Development with an opportunity for growth. Profile Motivated professional with studies in Computer Science Bachelor Program at Vancouver Island University possessing strong people skills and a record of reliability and hard work, excellent communication skills and ability to analyze and implement solutions for all levels of an organization. Education Vancouver Island University September 2010 – 2013 Nanaimo, BC Diploma in Computer Science Pursuing A Bachelor in Science with a major in Computer Science. (Seeking to finish a Network Security and Design Bachelors degree at BCIT) Escuela Superior de Computo September 2001 – June 2005 M Information Technology Diploma. Mexico City, Mexico Experience Freelance Web Development and Tech Support June 2010 – Present Nanaimo, BC n Website design and development. n Obtained contracts for the development of websites. n Most responsibilities as a freelancer is to locate potential customers, provide accurate information to sale my services, manage other people for larger projects. In big projects I have under my supervision an experienced SEO, and a Junior Programmer. n I had provided technical support to clients using Citrix servers, remote server connection, active directory, outlook exchange, Appriver, Bomgar, for clients using windows xp/8, Mac OS, and Linux. Using windows server 2003 or 2008 I was able to deliver an excellent customer service experience solving Internet connection issues, software, and hardware issues with remote support as well as onsite. Israel Acosta E-Mail: israel-acosta@hotmail.com 778-994-4996 LinkedIn: http://goo.gl/zIS2Z israelacosta.com Vancouver, BC. Hewlett-Packard June 2008 – June 2010 Mexico City, Mexico n Software and hardware specialist. Responsible for technical support of HP large format printers (HP_IPG) and sales of printer spare parts. n Worked with team members and met deadlines in a high-pressure environment. n Increased sales by 70% over one year and closed more than 25% of customer issues per month. n Provided technical support in Mexico City, after a few months of exceeding the job expectations I was asked to take over all Mexico. At the end of my position just after one year I was taking care of customer from all Mexico and Latin America providing customer service, technical support, hardware sales, and extended guaranties sales as well. Skills Software: n Windows xp/8/server, Mac OS X, Linux (Debian, Ubuntu, Fedora, Citrix) n Dreamweaver, Photoshop, InDesign, Eclipse, X-code, Coda and Microsoft Office. n Knowledge of Systems and Networks administration for Linux-based systems. n Advance Microsoft Excel n Appriver, Outlook Exchange, Bomgar, Active Directory. Programming: n Object Oriented Programing, C++, JavaScript, PHP, HTML5 and CSS3. n Learn and apply new programming languages quickly. Israel Acosta E-Mail: israel-acosta@hotmail.com 778-994-4996 LinkedIn: http://goo.gl/zIS2Z israelacosta.com Vancouver, BC. Interpersonal and Business Skills n Technical writing and Business Communication. n Work well with others and in high-pressure environments. n Work well with and without supervision. n Strategic thinking, interpersonal communication. n Familiar with modeling organizational systems n Agile modeling n Data flow diagrams and Object Oriented systems analysis. n Essentials of effective input and output, database design, and human computer interaction. Languages n Fluent in Spanish and English. Interests n I enjoy the outdoors life, my favorite outdoors sports are, snowboarding and soccer. n I like different type of books; some of my favorites are, marketing, psychology, and Neurology. n When I need to think and be relaxed I would grab my Spanish guitar and play a few chords. n Most recently I been investigating projects to do with my raspberry Pi. References Upon request </p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/israel-acosta/resume/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">881bb6cc-5c53-48f2-aac2-32a6487103b9</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2016 17:15:15 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>